# Jan Mirecki • Frontend Developer

I am a Frontend Developer and a Product Designer. I graduated in Product Design and after 4 years of professional experience as a UI & UX designer, I switched to a full-time developer role in 2015.

I work mostly with React, TypeScript & UI Design. I'm interested in high-quality projects focused strongly on the design, dedicated to regular internet users. I would be particularly happy to cooperate on a design system project. Other fields of my current professional role interests: QA, PM, and Product Designer.

In May 2024, I moved from Warsaw to Oslo, and since September last year, I have been learning Norwegian. I love Norway for its landscapes and vast mountain trails, and it was here that I caught my first fish early this spring A.

In my free time, I like to tinker, support friends with their projects, ride my motorcycle, climb, ski, and travel in my homemade micro rv. Recently, I started learning to skateboard, which brings me a lot of joy. I am very fond of coffee, kombucha, and bread of my own baking.

Polish **P** Native English 🗣 Advanced French • Conversational Norwegian 🗣 Beginner

Contact: +48 501 299 282 jan@strm.dev

≥ Email:

@janmirecki: https://www.linkedin.com/in/janmirecki/

**m** pdf strm.dev (eBook)

# Skills

## Core

Javascript • Typescript • HTML5 • CSS3

## Libs & Frameworks

React JS & TS · Astro.js · Redux · Vue · Tailwind CSS · Tailwind UI · HeadlessUI styled-components • Bootstrap 4 & 5 • AntD • Next.js • Gatsby

# Maintenance

Jest • React Testing Library • Webpack • Parcel • JIRA git • git hooks • npm • yarn • husky • eslint • prettier • bash • zsh

# Ⅲ & XU

Figma • Framer • Illustrator • InDesign • Photoshop • InVision Studio • Sketch

## More

Arduino • Lego Mindstorms • Adobe Scripting • ...

# **Experience**

# Aug 2022 - Now

#### **SZTORM**

🚨 Own Business > Senior Frontend Developer > Consultant > Architect

As a freelancer I'm cooperating with various parties, supporting commercial and non-profit projects. I have worked on projects supporting refugees. I organized a group of IT volunteers called WebScouts and supported more or less formal NGO organizations and grassroots initiatives. Together, we took part in accelerating the delivery of a Polish government website to support Ukraine. I led UX design exercises at the SWPS University in Warsaw, Department of Psychology and Computer Science. Commercially, I worked on the SAP UI for the US-based company – Corevist as a React Developer. Previously, I coordinated the redesign project of the web and mobile platform for Biletomat.pl, part of the Time For Friends Company. In this role, I led a team of designers, developers, and marketing professionals from a technical, coordination, and visual perspective, reporting directly to the company's management. Currently, I am coordinating work on a reservation system for facilities, where I am responsible for the frontend, design, and project management.

Ebert Studio > SWPS University > Biletomat.pl > Emagine > Corevist > Techlab EE pomagamukrainie.gov.pl > Fundacja Konflikt > Daydream Yachting

IT volunteering • Tech Leading • Frontend Development • Design Consulting • University Lecturer

# Aug 2019 - Aug 2021

# CD Projekt Red

🚨 Senior Frontend Developer > Tech Lead

Leading the team for designing and implementing a game (GWENT) Admin Panel in React Typescript integrated with the existing backend environment and creating tools for game management in a variety of frontend technologies. I was tech leading the team of 2 Frontend Developers (me + 1 mid/regular FD) and 3 Backend Developers (PHP). I was responsible for setting the development directions for the platform, writing documentation and manuals, leading the knowledge-sharing sessions for backend devs who were new in a React Frontend environment, and sharing our progress in front of the ~100 members of the Gwent Team on monthly meetings.

React TS • Redux • Saga Middleware • Typescript • Ant Design • Jest • React Testing Library • PHP • Symphony • Docker

# Jan 2019 - Aug 2019

## 🖩 Sztorm Jan Mirecki

🚨 Frontend Developer > Consultant > Architect

Landing pages development, web app development

Kłosy Knives - Laboratorium EE - Isobar-Dentsu Aegis Network

JavaScript • React JS • Gatsby • Karma + Jasmine • SASS • Bootstrap 4 • GIT

#### Oct 2017 - Oct 2018

# Onwelo

🚨 Frontend Developer

Frontend for banking, financial, and moto industry CMRs, migrations, and internal product development.

JavaScript • React JS • Angular 5 • Karma + Jasmine • SASS • Bootstrap 4 • GIT • Docker

## Dec 2016 - Sep 2017

## Avon Cosmetics Polska

Frontend Developer

Landing pages, mailing templates, and corporate services supporting: Avon Online, Avon Representative Suite.

HTML • SASS • Bootstrap 3 • GIT • Adobe: Xd / Ai / Ps / Indd

#### Oct 2015 - Nov 2016

## Laboratorium EE

🚇 Frontend Developer > UX Designer

RWD websites and landing pages

HTML5 • SASS/SCSS • Bootstrap 3 • Material Design • NPM • Adobe: Ai, Ps • Teamworking with GIT in SCRUM with JIRA

## Jan 2015 - Jan 2016

#### **Freelancer**

Frontend Developer > UI Designer

Website and app design, mockup prototyping, print design.

Docs Against Gravity , pracowniajasiewicz.com , laboratorium.ee , mariaerikssonstudio.com , Caritas Polska , NOTO Studio , Jan Strumiłło Architekt , malunkimarka.com

# Jul 2012 - Sep 2014

#### Laboratorium EE

🙎 UX > UI designer

Website and app design, mockup prototyping. Laboratorium EE identity design: logotype, internal documents, data design, website design, and frontend coding

HTML • CSS • Bootstrap • RWD • Adobe Ai, Ps, Id

# **Education**

## Oct 2016 - Jun 2017

😰 SWPS University of Social Sciences and Humanities 📍 Warsaw, Poland

Postgraduate Studies of Creative Coding

# Dec 2010 - May 2011

ENSAAMA Olivier de Serres 
Paris, France

Erasmus student exchange

Product Design on Faculty of Industrial Design

# Oct 2008 - Sep 2014

🛍 Academy of Fine Arts 📍 Warsaw, Poland

Bachelor's in **Product Design**Faculty of Industrial Design